<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kemal Tekce</title>
    <link>https://kmltkc.de/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Kemal Tekce</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://kmltkc.de/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>conscious neuroplasticity.</title>
      <link>https://kmltkc.de/037_conscious-neuroplasticity/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kmltkc.de/037_conscious-neuroplasticity/</guid>
      <description>During school, we didn’t have to be consciously aware of our learning. We didn’t go to school while actively thinking “Today I’m going to learn more about quadratic equations, cell biology, and how to write an essay.”. Learning just happened. Even if we didn’t feel like it.
This is because the young brain is a learning and plasticity machine. The necessary chemicals and neuromodulators are already there in our brain. Ready to go.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>learning is like a frustrating puzzle.</title>
      <link>https://kmltkc.de/036_learning_frustrating_puzzle/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kmltkc.de/036_learning_frustrating_puzzle/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes learning can be really frustrating. Either you are trying to understand a concept and the penny just won’t drop or you are trying to use a new skill but it just won’t work. It takes a lot of effort.
But it also feels like a puzzle. A puzzle you can easily obsess with. A puzzle you muddle through. And at some point, the penny just drops. It works. It finally makes sense.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>the important connection between thinking and feeling.</title>
      <link>https://kmltkc.de/035_thinking_and_feeling/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kmltkc.de/035_thinking_and_feeling/</guid>
      <description>Thinking and feeling are often discussed separately. We view them as different activities. For example, we believe that learning is solely a thinking activity. But thinking and feeling might be blended together more than we expect.
Thinking and feeling are not separated. They are connected. Every thought we have triggers an emotion we feel. Every feeling we have triggers a thought we think.
You might think about some deadlines you have and get stressed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>learn to iterate. iterate to learn.</title>
      <link>https://kmltkc.de/034_learn_to_iterate/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kmltkc.de/034_learn_to_iterate/</guid>
      <description>I only realize it now but my Physics studies taught me something unconsciously that changed my perspective and mindset drastically. And, grasping its importance now, I think this should be taught and learnt consciously — not only as a side effect but as a clear goal.
Often we think and act very one-dimensionally. We do the same thing over and over again while expecting another result. We might learn with the same methods expecting better results.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 techniques to improve your focus.</title>
      <link>https://kmltkc.de/033_improve_focus/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kmltkc.de/033_improve_focus/</guid>
      <description>I used to struggle with my focus a lot. And I still do from time to time. But it got better. If I wanted to focus on what I was doing, I would easily get distracted. Sometimes my focus was so off that I didn’t even start doing what I wanted to do.
I spent a lot of time planning. I was psyched to learn, to read, to work on personal projects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>why learn the basics.</title>
      <link>https://kmltkc.de/032_why_learn_basics/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kmltkc.de/032_why_learn_basics/</guid>
      <description>Online learning, MOOCs, books, tutorials make it easy to jump into a topic and start learning. You might see a course that sparks your curiosity — for me, it is courses around Data Science or UX Design — and you just want to start diving into it. You are super curious and motivated.
You are so excited that you rush through the first few parts. You just want to get to the faster, to the interesting and more complex topics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>the learning mindset after university.</title>
      <link>https://kmltkc.de/031_learning_mindset_after_university/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kmltkc.de/031_learning_mindset_after_university/</guid>
      <description>My learning mindset changed after school and during university. Learning in university was fundamentally different from learning in school. I had to change and learn differently to finish university and avoid failing.
The change was basically to adopt new learning techniques. There are a lot of evidence-based and scientifically proven learning techniques to master university. The methods that helped me the most are categorization, active recall, spaced repetition, and interleaving. Or as I like to call it: CASI.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>emotions and learning.</title>
      <link>https://kmltkc.de/030_emotions_and_learning/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kmltkc.de/030_emotions_and_learning/</guid>
      <description>Learning feels great again. I learnt some basic UX Design skills, how to use Figma, and how to program with Vue.js. I even had a learning project and was able to build the first prototype of my digital bullet journal — dibujo. I even have a learning system in place which I enjoy using. So learning feels great — I thought.
Lately, I again fell into old patterns and started struggling again with learning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>the trap of being a curious learner.</title>
      <link>https://kmltkc.de/029_trap_of_curious_learner/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kmltkc.de/029_trap_of_curious_learner/</guid>
      <description>I usually like sitting down, reading a book or watching a tutorial, and trying to apply what I learnt. It feels good to learn new things. Until, one day, it didn’t feel great anymore.
Being a curious learner holds a trap.
There are a lot of interesting topics to learn. You might get exposed to new areas and interesting insights from different topics through tutorials, books, podcasts. Even a little side note or hint from the creator might spark your curiosity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>don’t only take time to learn.</title>
      <link>https://kmltkc.de/028_dont_only_take_time_to_learn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kmltkc.de/028_dont_only_take_time_to_learn/</guid>
      <description>For a long time, I thought learning is just about consuming information, understanding insights, and using the knowledge to build experience.
But if you want to learn, you also have to take time outside of consuming, understanding, and applying. You have to take time to reflect. Take time to explore. Take time to tinker. Take time to rest.
Reflect to see if your learning is going well. Reflect on your understanding by expressing your understanding.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>the benefit of doubt.</title>
      <link>https://kmltkc.de/027_the_benefit_of_doubt/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kmltkc.de/027_the_benefit_of_doubt/</guid>
      <description>I often have a feeling of doubt. I doubt myself. I doubt my skills and knowledge. I doubt my ability to solve problems. Sometimes life just feels too uncertain.
This is why I started to priorizite learning more and more. I learn to beat uncertainty. I learn to get rid of the feeling of doubt.
But be careful. Don’t make the same mistake I did. Don’t have the goal to beat uncertainty and eradicate doubt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>build a learning habit.</title>
      <link>https://kmltkc.de/026_build_a_learning_habit/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kmltkc.de/026_build_a_learning_habit/</guid>
      <description>Our life is constantly changing. Our interests may change too. We will face new obstacles. All of this can create a feeling of uncertainty and anxiety in us.
Learning might help us to deal with all this.
Learning is a skill that is becoming more and more important. Learning does not stop after school. It does not stop after university. Learning keeps you mentally fit. Learning can help you adjust to change.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>consistent goal.</title>
      <link>https://kmltkc.de/024_consistent_goal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kmltkc.de/024_consistent_goal/</guid>
      <description>Do you feel like everything seems interesting? As in my case: Programming, Typography, Data Science, UX Design, Physics, Psychology. You want to learn everything. But there is not enough time. So maybe you learn a bit of this and a bit of that?
I felt like that and I did it like that. And, it wasn’t great.
I never had a consistent learning goal.
If you don’t have a consistent goal, you run the risk of only scratching the surface on a lot of different areas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>learning is frustrating.</title>
      <link>https://kmltkc.de/025_learning_is_frustrating/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kmltkc.de/025_learning_is_frustrating/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s Monday morning and I am watching my kid play with his stackable cups. He is improving his motor skills and tries to learn how to stack these cups.
He is fully focused, calm and concentrated. He is in an ideal flow state. It is remarkable. It seems like nothing can distract him. He is just trying and tinkering to put one cup on top of another. He fails and succeeds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>learn to play. play to learn.</title>
      <link>https://kmltkc.de/023_learn_to_play/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kmltkc.de/023_learn_to_play/</guid>
      <description>As a child, we had this natural curiosity and natural discipline. Everything seemed like a mystery and we were curious about it. We learnt a lot by being immersed in what we were doing.
Nowadays learning feels like a drill. It is forced. We force ourselves. We turned our natural discipline into an unnaturally forced discipline. The reason might be that we lost touch with playing.
We lost our playfulness and became more work-full.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>design your learning experience.</title>
      <link>https://kmltkc.de/022_design_your_learning_experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kmltkc.de/022_design_your_learning_experience/</guid>
      <description>I never found the perfect online course. Something was always missing. Either it was too easy or too difficult. Too theoretical without practices or too shallow without deeper understanding. I never had a great learning experience.
Who is to blame? Who should take on the responsibility? Something should change.
Most online courses might seem boring. They are just too content- and knowledge-focused and less action- and experience-focused. This means you learn a lot of facts but don’t get to use them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>enjoy learning.</title>
      <link>https://kmltkc.de/021_enjoy_learning/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kmltkc.de/021_enjoy_learning/</guid>
      <description>I drag myself to learn. I have no motivation. I force myself to sit down and spend minutes, hours, even days taking notes, thinking, trying to understand. I drained a lot of energy just by thinking about having to learn. Learning can have a lot of mundane parts we have to do.
But then, some days it feels like the opposite is true. It is not draggy. I have the motivation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>goals in learning.</title>
      <link>https://kmltkc.de/020_goals_in_learning/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kmltkc.de/020_goals_in_learning/</guid>
      <description>I used to set goals for my learning.
Whenever I encounter an interesting online course, I decide to take it. I sign up. I check out the course content. I define as my goal to finish the course in 4 weeks.
Now, how often did that work out for me? Did I enjoy learning? Sadly, no; and it didn’t work out quite well. I started to lose hope and trust in goals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>don’t ignore your curiosity.</title>
      <link>https://kmltkc.de/019_dont_ignore_your_curiosity/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kmltkc.de/019_dont_ignore_your_curiosity/</guid>
      <description>You sit down for learning. Pen and paper ready — or keyboard and note-taking app if you are more of a digital learner. You consume content. You let it sit in your mind, think, and try to understand. Out of nowhere, you stumble and ask yourself: “What? Why does it work like this?”
This is your curiosity kicking in. What do you do in these situations?
Do you disregard it? Do you ignore it?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>find your obsession.</title>
      <link>https://kmltkc.de/018_find_your_obsession/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kmltkc.de/018_find_your_obsession/</guid>
      <description>The mainstream advice for finding the right career is “Find your passion.” or “Ask yourself: What is your passion?”. I’m asking this myself a lot. I think I can only make it, once I found my passion. But I always come to the same conclusions.
I either have a lot of passions or no true passion. I can be passionate about a lot of things. I enjoy programming with Python, I enjoy writing about learning, I enjoy reading and learning itself, I enjoy designing with Figma — and the list goes on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>knowledge is not the goal.</title>
      <link>https://kmltkc.de/017_knowlegdge_is_not_the_goal/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kmltkc.de/017_knowlegdge_is_not_the_goal/</guid>
      <description>Each day holds subtle differences to be curious about and to learn more about. You might read an article and highlight a specific sentence. You might watch a YouTube video with an interesting insight and take a quick note. You might take part in an online course and try to understand what is being taught.
But, to truly learn, we can’t only rely on consuming information, on being able to remember it, or on understanding it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>unkowns in learning.</title>
      <link>https://kmltkc.de/016_unkowns_in_learning/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kmltkc.de/016_unkowns_in_learning/</guid>
      <description>It feels exciting to take on a new journey — journeys from starting a new career over starting a new project to going on vacation. But every journey comes with its own uncertainties and unknowns. We can’t know everything beforehand. Planning a new journey doesn’t cover the unknown.
Depending on how we see unknowns, how we think about them, and how we deal with them, they might be either a source of energy or they might drain our energy without hesitation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>confidence.</title>
      <link>https://kmltkc.de/015_confidence/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kmltkc.de/015_confidence/</guid>
      <description>We are sitting in front of one tiny thing we are trying to learn — for hours. But we just don’t get our head around it. Learning can get difficult. Learning can be frustrating. Learning can make us even feel stupid and want to quit.
But don’t give up. Have confidence and believe in your skills and abilities to learn. Make mistakes, face obstacles, and take the time you need to understand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>intentional learning. system.</title>
      <link>https://kmltkc.de/014_intentional_learning_system/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kmltkc.de/014_intentional_learning_system/</guid>
      <description>We have a goal. We want to learn. The first thing we do is create a plan. In self-learning, we most often look for an online course that matches what we want to learn. Ideally, they already have divided the curriculum into multiple weeks with timestamps on how long each material takes. We take it and our planning is done.
But then we miss one material. We try to keep up with the content and don’t take time to fill gaps in our understanding.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>montessori mindset.</title>
      <link>https://kmltkc.de/013_montessori_mindset/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kmltkc.de/013_montessori_mindset/</guid>
      <description>There are differences between traditional education and Montessori education. One of them is dominating at our schools and also made their way heavily into online learning. Online learning is more and more content-focused — losing their learners along the way. The Montessori approach has a lot to offer for how we teach our children. But maybe it is also the secret to improve online learning and self-learning.
Instead of a top-down education where the educator tells the student what to learn, the Montessori method embraces a more free and flexible style of learning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mistakes.</title>
      <link>https://kmltkc.de/012_learning_quote_three_mistakes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kmltkc.de/012_learning_quote_three_mistakes/</guid>
      <description>When we learn, we have the goal of mastering a skill. We want to become the expert. Sadly, because of these expecations we don’t see learning as a journey towards mastery.
We avoid trying, experimenting, and making mistakes. We just don’t want to look stupid. But if we truly want to learn we have to make mistakes. Like Ray Congdon said:
“Anything worth doing well is worth doing poorly at first.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>intentional learning.</title>
      <link>https://kmltkc.de/011_intentional_learning/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kmltkc.de/011_intentional_learning/</guid>
      <description>Everyone and everything is fighting for our attention. And, we try to keep up with everything. We try to consume more and more to stay in touch with everyone. We try to do more and more just to feel productive.
We divide our attention across so many things; which sadly means nothing is getting the attention it deserves, and it makes us feel terrible.
This is not only true for our private and professional life but also for our learning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>obstacles.</title>
      <link>https://kmltkc.de/010_learning_quote_two_obstacles/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kmltkc.de/010_learning_quote_two_obstacles/</guid>
      <description>We like being comfortable — especially in our learning. We read what we are already familiar with. We revisit what we already know. We practice what we’ve already mastered. This feels nice. It feels like we are learning so much. But sadly, we keep up an illusion. And this can be devastating.
We try to avoid discomfort. We don’t like exposing gaps in our knowledge. We almost hate facing obstacles. They make us anxious.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>feedback ladder.</title>
      <link>https://kmltkc.de/009_feedback_ladder/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kmltkc.de/009_feedback_ladder/</guid>
      <description>The number of available online courses is increasing. Universities are offering lectures online. Schools are testing remote lessons. All in all, remote as well as self-learning is rising and with it the importance of proper self-feedback during learning.
Feedback is essential for learning. But it is hard to include feedback properly during learning and even harder during self-learning.
You might have prepared some notes and you are learning by self-quizzing and self-explaining.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>understanding.</title>
      <link>https://kmltkc.de/008_learning_quote_one_understanding/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kmltkc.de/008_learning_quote_one_understanding/</guid>
      <description>Often, we only engage in shallow learning. We decide to learn something new. We, for example, choose a new online course or join a new Bootcamp program to learn a new skill. We are excited and want to learn. But in the end, we only rush through the materials. We try to take notes but end up taking transcripts. Our learning ends up shallow.
This shallow learning creates a feeling of frustration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>learning trifecta.</title>
      <link>https://kmltkc.de/007_learning_trifecta/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kmltkc.de/007_learning_trifecta/</guid>
      <description>I took a bunch of online courses from an Introduction to Psychology course to a Design Principles course. From a UX Design course to an Artificial intelligence course. There is one thing I learnt for sure — learning is difficult. I always had the feeling that my learning process wasn’t the best —and it probably still isn’t. There was always something that is missing. I either rushed the materials and didn’t take the time to understand the mentioned ideas or I took the time to understand but didn’t use the ideas in a personal project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>three questions.</title>
      <link>https://kmltkc.de/006_three_questions/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kmltkc.de/006_three_questions/</guid>
      <description>Do you ever have the feeling of perplexity when you are learning something and you think “I should know this. I’ve just read it. Why can’t I remember?”
This is because of the illusion of knowledge. And I fall into this trap almost every time I read. I just have to turn the page and I immediately forget what I just read.
Itis easy to fall into the “illusion of knowledge” trap.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>fight forgetting.</title>
      <link>https://kmltkc.de/005_fight_forgetting/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kmltkc.de/005_fight_forgetting/</guid>
      <description>I grab my Kindle and go to our balcony. It’s time to read a bit. I’m currently reading “A Mind For Numbers”. It contains a ton of interesting insights regarding learning. So I’m highlighting, highlighting, and highlighting.
Later, after I’m done reading, I’ll transfer all the highlights to Notion.
It is a great feeling to find new insightful information. It feels surprising and familiar at the same time. So naturally, I want to hold on to the insight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>learning hack.</title>
      <link>https://kmltkc.de/004_learning_hack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kmltkc.de/004_learning_hack/</guid>
      <description>I pick up my phone and start scrolling through Medium. I’m looking for articles on how to improve my learning. And let’s be honest: there is a ton of articles out there. I already read a few books and watched a few YouTube videos regarding learning, looking for more and more learning hacks. While scrolling I remember. I saved an article yesterday about 5 skills to learn; and one of these skills was learning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>keep learning.</title>
      <link>https://kmltkc.de/003_keep_learning/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kmltkc.de/003_keep_learning/</guid>
      <description>I’m back in the office. I’m back in front of the problem I avoided for the last couple of days. Luckily I was busy with other tasks. Luckily I had to take care of other problems first. But now there is no getting around it anymore.
I avoided it because I have never faced a problem like this before. I don’t have the skills to solve it fast. I first have to read and learn a bit more about it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>learn less.</title>
      <link>https://kmltkc.de/002_learn_less/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kmltkc.de/002_learn_less/</guid>
      <description>I just had breakfast and now it’s time for learning. Super excited. I go to my desk. I open my laptop, I open up Notion — my favourite note-taking app — , and I open the UX Design online course which I’m currently doing on Coursera.
I’m super excited because I want to learn more about UX Design. I’m curious and I think it might be helpful in the future. Maybe one day I’ll find it useful for my job or for my own products.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>struggles.</title>
      <link>https://kmltkc.de/001_struggles/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kmltkc.de/001_struggles/</guid>
      <description>It is Friday morning. It is my learning day. I wake up. Get ready. And start learning. I enjoy learning new skills. This time I want to learn more about creating websites. My goal is to build a digital bullet journal prototype.
At least this was the plan. The last couple of Fridays I struggled with learning. I’m either lacking the energy, or I’m getting distracted easily, or I’m planning too much for the day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>📚 medium.</title>
      <link>https://kmltkc.de/projects/00_medium/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kmltkc.de/projects/00_medium/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>🎒 lean learning.</title>
      <link>https://kmltkc.de/projects/01_leanlearning/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kmltkc.de/projects/01_leanlearning/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>🎧 notion - learning template.</title>
      <link>https://kmltkc.de/projects/02_notionlearning/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kmltkc.de/projects/02_notionlearning/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>✏️ dibujo - the digital bullet journal.</title>
      <link>https://kmltkc.de/projects/03_dibujo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kmltkc.de/projects/03_dibujo/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>🚲 data science practice story.</title>
      <link>https://kmltkc.de/projects/04_dspracticestory/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kmltkc.de/projects/04_dspracticestory/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>🤖 scraping course.</title>
      <link>https://kmltkc.de/projects/05_scraping/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kmltkc.de/projects/05_scraping/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
