<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kemal Tekce</title>
    <link>https://kmltkc.de/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Kemal Tekce</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://kmltkc.de/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Learning should be flexible.</title>
      <link>https://kmltkc.de/006_post/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kmltkc.de/006_post/</guid>
      <description>Are you excited to learn? Did you find an interesting online-course? With motivation and excitement, you start learning. But after some time the initial spark fades away? Learning feels like a burden? Almost like it became the source that drains your energy?
You ask yourself: What happened? Wasn’t I excited about this?
This happened to me. And I think a more flexible and open-space learning approach might fix this problem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to increase your reading speed?</title>
      <link>https://kmltkc.de/005_post/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kmltkc.de/005_post/</guid>
      <description>Do you like reading books? Are you eager to read more and absorb all the great insights? Do you watch YouTube videos in which your favourite content creators talk about all the books they are reading and you want to keep up?
Yes, yes, and yes. To achieve all this, I thought “maybe I have to increase my reading speed.”. So I sat down and watched — a few more YouTube videos about how to read faster.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rediscovering rereading as a learning method.</title>
      <link>https://kmltkc.de/004_post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kmltkc.de/004_post/</guid>
      <description>How do you read books? How do you catch insights from books? How do you learn from books? Do you read, highlight, and take notes? At some point, you might want to repeat what you read to process, understand, and learn. But what are good learning techniques to accomplish this?
Self-testing and active recall. Both help you challenge your understanding, spot gaps in your understanding, and guide you in your learning process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Journey to an intentional life by being a time pessimist.</title>
      <link>https://kmltkc.de/003_post/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kmltkc.de/003_post/</guid>
      <description>Do you have a huge to-do list day in day out? Does your to-do list contain things that you have to do and things you want to do? Things that you are curious and passionate about? But you don’t get them all done? Isn’t that frustrating?
I plan to read, write, take notes, code, and learn something new. To be able to cross out these to-dos I do a little bit of everything and busy around half-hearted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What memorization experts can teach us about learning.</title>
      <link>https://kmltkc.de/002_post/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kmltkc.de/002_post/</guid>
      <description>This might not be what you expect. This is not about a fancy memorization technique like the memory palace that experts use. It is something much more simple and elegant which could change how we should learn. It is what is behind the memory palace. The fundamental thing we as humans are actually primed to do but almost never do if it comes to true learning.
We all want to learn and improve and grow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hero’s learning journey.</title>
      <link>https://kmltkc.de/001_post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kmltkc.de/001_post/</guid>
      <description>While learning more about writing and storytelling styles, I came across the hero’s journey storytelling method. While reading about the hero’s journey, I started to think whether or not the hero’s journey is the journey we take — or ideally, we should take — for learning.
The hero’s journey — or our learning journey — often starts with realizing the mundane reality and discovering a new mysterious world. In our case, the mysterious world is a topic which catches our interest.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
